Guide to the Frances Hesselbein Papers, 1942-2013 AIS.2013.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Frances Hesselbein Institute Papers, 1942-2014; A.
  - Peter F. Drucker files, 1942-2011; VI.
    - Correspondence, 1990-2005 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Documentary information, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Drucker bibliography, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Drucker quotes, 2000s (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Biographic data, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Speeches by Peter Drucker, 1989-1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Speeches about Peter Drucker, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Peter Drucker 90th birthday celebration, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Drucker Graduate School of Management information, September 2001 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Drucker - Hesselbein photograph, 1990s (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Drucker publicity photos, undated (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Drucker Archives and Institute information, 1992-2011 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Peter F. Drucker Academy information, 2000s (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Presidential Medal of Freedom materials, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Warren Bennis-Peter Drucker video materials, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - The Drucker Project: A Transnational Opportunity, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Drucker - Nobel Prize possibility discussion, 1996 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Hesselbein Fellows, 1997-2004; VII.
    The Frances Hesselbein Community Innovation Fellows program was a project with the Drucker Foundation to promote the leaders of nonprofit organizations and give them the opportunities to improve both their organizations and the world around them. Fellows applied with a specific goal in mind for their organization and the ways in which they thought to accomplish these tasks, and after being selected were given a mentor from the management community. Those chosen were also provided various opportunities to meet and discuss topics with other leaders during their year-long appointment. This series contains information on applicants from the years 1997-2002, as well as various pieces of writing from different Fellows, schedules of events, and selection committee materials. We do ask researchers to sign a letter of confidentiality when accessing these files.
    Access Restrictions
    Researcher access to Subgroup A., Series VII. Hesselbein Fellows is subject to the Archives & Special Collections confidentiality agreement.
    - Hesselbein Fellows Selection Committee materials, June 29, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Selection Committee materials, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 28-29)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Selection Committee materials, June 25, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 30-31)
    - Fellows planning meeting information, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Program Development, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Hesselbein Fellows application information, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Barbara Coscarello, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Aura Comacho Maas, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Danielle Pensley, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Craig Soaries, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Dolores Barrett, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Michael Neely, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - James Williams, 1998-1999 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Marjorie Bush, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Vivian Clecak, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Leon Haynes, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Jan Owen, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Robert Pedersen, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Mounir Sharobeem, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Eric Bachrach, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - R. Mark Davis, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Douglas Shenson, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Horacio Trujillo, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Pamela Winters-Colbert, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Cathey Brown, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Ashfaq Ishaq, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Thang Dinh Nguyen, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Sven Schumacher, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Marilyn Sullivan, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Kathy Augustine, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Rosalie Cates, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 59)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Michael Duggan, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 60)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Julie Evans, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 61)
    - Hesselbein Fellows Application - Paul Furrh, 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 62)
    - Fellows' writings, 1998-2004 (Box 14, Folder 63)
    - Hesselbein Fellows correspondence/communications, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 64)
    - Correspondence w/ Fellows, 2004-2007 (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Correspondence about Fellows, 1998-1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Hesselbein Fellows funding plans, 1995-1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Audio/Visual material, 1985-2013, undated; VIII.
    This series contains the audio and video recordings for the Frances Hesselbein Institute subgroup. Materials in this series include video cassette tapes, audio cassette tapes, CD-ROMs, DVDs, and various forms of photographic images. Most of the videos were produced by the Drucker Foundation and Leader to Leader Institute, and a large number of the video and audio cassette tapes feature recordings from the conferences held by these institutions throughout the years. There are also videos of Peter Drucker speeches, and seminars run by Frances Hesselbein. The Drucker Foundation subseries contains four unidentified boxes of open reel audio tape. The A/V materials have been arranged within each subseries starting with the oldest formats, such as Betacam or VHS tapes, and ending with the last, usually DVDs. Multiple formats of some productions were kept to ensure preservation of the content.
    - The Peter F. Drucker Foundation, 1991-2002, 2008; 1.
      - 1991 Annual Drucker Conference - Showcase on Innovation (Box 33, Video 1)
      - The Drucker Foundation Nonprofit Management Seminars - "Self-Assessment as an Evaluation and Planning Tool", March 4, 1992 (Box 33, Video 2)
      - The Drucker Foundation Nonprofit Management Seminars - "Managing for the Future", June 12, 1992 (Box 33, Video 3)
      - The Drucker Foundation Nonprofit Management Seminar - "A Crucial Partnership", July 15, 1992 (Box 33, Video 4)
      - 1996 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 1 - Panel discussion, November 1, 1996 (Box 33, Video 5)
      - 1996 Annual Drucker Conference - Tape 1 fix, November 1996 (Box 33, Video 6)
      - 1996 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 2 - Panel discussion, November 1, 1996 (Box 33, Video 7)
      - 1996 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 3 - Dinner and Awards Show, November 1, 1996 (Box 33, Video 8)
      - 1996 Annual Drucker Conference - Tape 3 fix, November 1996 (Box 33, Video 9)
      - 1996 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 4 - Hesselbein introduces Christine Letts, Kevin Kelly, and Peter Drucker, November 2, 1996 (Box 33, Video 10)
      - 1996 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 5 - Panel discussion, November 2, 1996 (Box 33, Video 11)
      - "The Future of Organization" Conference Board meeting, September 19, 1997 (Box 33, Video 12)
      - Conference Board 1998 - Organization of the Future conference, February 20, 1998 (Box 33, Video 13)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 4 - Esther Dyson and Roundtable, November 9, 1998 (Box 33, Video 14)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 5 - Roundtable w/ Dyson, Collins, etc., November 9, 1998 (Box 33, Video 15)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 10 - Self Assessment Work Session, November 9, 1998 (Box 33, Video 16)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 11 - Self-Assessment Work Session part 2, November 9, 1998 (Box 33, Video 17)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 12 - Self-Assessment Work Session part 3, November 9, 1998 (Box 33, Video 18)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 13 - Self-Assessment Work Session part 4, November 9, 1998 (Box 33, Video 19)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 14 - Peter Drucker pre-dinner, November 9, 1998 (Box 33, Video 20)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 14 - Self-Assessment panel and Drucker Award dinner opening, November 9, 1998 (Box 33, Video 21)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 18 - Leonard Schlesinger, November 10, 1998 (Box 33, Video 22)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 19 - Leonard Schlesinger part 2, November 10, 1998 (Box 33, Video 23)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 20 - Final Roundtable, November 10, 1998 (Box 33, Video 24)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 21 - Final Roundtable part 2, November 10, 1998 (Box 33, Video 25)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 22 - Final Roundtable part 3, November 10, 1998 (Box 33, Video 26)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 1 - Skill to Guide 2, November 7, 1999 (Box 34, Video 1)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 2 - Skill to Guide 2, November 7, 1999 (Box 34, Video 2)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 3 - Skill to Guide 2, November 7, 1999 (Box 34, Video 3)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 4 - Skill to Guide 2, November 7, 1999 (Box 34, Video 4)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 5 - Skill to Guide 2 and Courage to Lead, November 7, 1999 (Box 34, Video 5)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 6 - Courage to Lead 1, November 7, 1999 (Box 34, Video 6)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 7 - Skill to Guide 1, November 7, 1999 (Box 34, Video 7)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 8 - Courage to Lead 2, November 7, 1999 (Box 34, Video 8)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 9 - Courage to Lead 2, Opening Plenary and Margaret Wheatly, November 7-8, 1999 (Box 34, Video 9)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 10 - M. Wheatly pt. 2, November 8, 1999 (Box 34, Video 10)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 11 - M. Wheatly pt. 3 and Lunch intro by P. Drucker, November 8, 1999 (Box 34, Video 11)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 12 - Lunch: F. Hesselbein, November 8, 1999 (Box 34, Video 12)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 13 - PFD 90th Birthday reception and dinner, November 1999 (Box 34, Video 13)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 14 - Dinner, November 8, 1999 (Box 34, Video 14)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 17 - Tue. A.M., November 9, 1999 (Box 34, Video 15)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 18 - Panel Discussion, November 9, 1999 (Box 34, Video 16)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 19 - Peter Drucker speech, November 1999 (Box 34, Video 17)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 20 - Peter Drucker closing remarks, November 1999 (Box 34, Video 18)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 1 - Opening Plenary, October 30, 2000 (Box 34, Video 19)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 2 - Dee Hock & "The Art of Chaordic Leadership", October 30, 2000 (Box 34, Video 20)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 3 - Dee Hock pt. 2 and Q and A, October 30, 2000 (Box 34, Video 21)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 4 - Dee Hock Q and A pt. 2, October 30, 2000 (Box 34, Video 22)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 7 - Lunchtime speech, Dorothy Ridings and "Communicating Philanthropy", October 30, 2000 (Box 34, Video 23)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 8 - Dorothy Ridings Q and A, October 30, 2000 (Box 34, Video 24)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 9 - Innovation Award Dinner, October 2000 (Box 34, Video 25)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 10 - Christina Gold and "Marketing for Innovation", October 2000 (Box 34, Video 26)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 11 - Christina Gold Q and A, William Bridges presentation, October 31, 2000 (Box 34, Video 27)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 12 - William Bridges and "Leading Transition", October 31, 2000 (Box 34, Video 28)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 13 - William Bridges Q and A, October 31, 2000 (Box 34, Video 29)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 14 - Closing Plenary, October 31, 2000 (Box 34, Video 30)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 15 - Closing Plenary, October 31, 2000 (Box 34, Video 31)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference Tape 16 - Birthday wishes for Frances, October 31, 2000 (Box 34, Video 32)
      - "Change Leaders" - Drucker/Senge Conversation, February 4, 2000 (Box 34, Video 33)
      - Peter Drucker for the Drucker Foundation/Conference Board, February 4, 2002 (Box 34, Video 34)
      - Drucker Foundation/Conference Board conference, February 2002 (Box 34, Video 35)
      - Adventure in Excellence symposium - Frances Hesselbein speech, 1990s (Box 34, Video 36)
      - Seminar by Satellite: Nonprofit Leader of the Future - Interviews post-session, November 12, 1997 (Box 34, Video 37)
      - "Drucker on Leaders", November 13, 1997 (Box 34, Video 38)
      - "Peer Education' - Drucker Foundation, November 20, 2000 (Box 34, Video 39)
      - The Peter F. Drucker Foundation Showcase on Innovation, November 13, 1991 (Box 35, Video 1)
      - Robert Buford and Richard Schubert - The Drucker Foundation's Showcase on Innovation, November 13, 1991 (Box 35, Video 2)
      - The Peter F. Drucker Foundation for Nonprofit Management - The First Annual Drucker Innovation Award, November 12, 1991 (Box 35, Video 3)
      - Lane Adams - The Drucker Foundation's Award dinner, November 12, 1991 (Box 35, Video 4)
      - Drucker Award winner 1991 - Judson Center, November 1991 (Box 35, Video 5)
      - Judson Center on Today Show, January 17, 1992 (Box 35, Video 6)
      - "Judson Center" on NBC Nightly News - L.I.F.E. Program, July 15, 1993 (Box 35, Video 7)
      - The Judson Center's L.I.F.E. Program, 1990s (Box 35, Video 8)
      - Frances Hesselbein Fellows Tribute, November 1, 1996 (Box 35, Video 9)
      - The Computer Clubhouse Broadcast excerpts, 1990s (Box 35, Video 10)
      - The Organization of the Future Conference - Peter Drucker Response to Questions, February 20, 1998 (Box 35, Video 11)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Esther Dyson and Roundtable (Box 35, Video 12)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Roundtable with Esther Dyson, Jim Collins, etc. (Box 35, Video 13)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Self-Assessment Tool Work Session (Box 35, Video 14)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Self-Assessment Tool Work Session part 2 (Box 35, Video 15)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Self-Assessment Tool Work Session part 3 (Box 35, Video 16)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Self-Assessment Tool Work Session part 4 (Box 35, Video 17)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Peter Drucker pre-dinner (Box 35, Video 18)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Final Roundtable (Box 35, Video 19)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Final Roundtable part 2 (Box 35, Video 20)
      - The Drucker Foundation - "Lessons in Leadership", 1998 (Box 35, Video 21)
      - The Drucker Foundation - "Excellence in Nonprofit Leadership", 1998 (Box 35, Video 22)
      - The Drucker Foundation Nonprofit Management Seminars - "Self-Assessment", 1992 (Box 35, Video 23)
      - The Drucker Foundation - "Managing for the Future", 1990s (Box 35, Video 24)
      - "Kids for Character" Character Counts! Coalition - Peter F. Drucker Canadian Foundation, September 7, 1995 (Box 35, Video 25)
      - The Peter F. Drucker Canadian Foundation - Kids Count, October 20, 1997 (Box 35, Video 26)
      - The Drucker Foundation Management Conference - fine cut, April 9, 1992 (Box 36, Video 1)
      - The Drucker Foundation Nonprofit Management Seminars, 1992 (Box 36, Video 2)
      - A Crucial Partnership: Roles of Board and Executives, 1992 (Box 36, Video 3)
      - Framing the Future: New Tools for Social Sector Leaders conference - First Plenary, Second Plenary pt. 1, April 1995 (Box 36, Video 4)
      - Framing the Future: New Tools for Social Sector Leaders conference - Second Plenary pt. 2, Third Plenary, April 1995 (Box 36, Video 5)
      - Framing the Future: New Tools for Social Sector Leaders conference - Fourth Plenary, April 11, 1995 (Box 36, Video 6)
      - Framing the Future: New Tools for Social Sector Leaders conference - Fourth Plenary, Fifth Plenary, April 1995 (Box 36, Video 7)
      - "Leader of the Future", April 4, 1996 (Box 36, Video 8)
      - CEL/Drucker Conference - Peter Drucker presentation, May 3, 1996 (Box 36, Video 9)
      - Peter F. Drucker on "The Future of Organizations" - Organization of the Future conference, 1998 (Box 36, Video 10)
      - Peter F. Drucker and Peter M. Senge "Change Leaders" - The Organization of the Future conference, 2000 (Box 36, Video 11)
      - Seminar in China video, October 2000 (Box 36, Video 12)
      - Peter F. Drucker discusses "From Ownership to Strategic Purpose" - Organization of the Future conference, 2002 (Box 36, Video 13)
      - International Seminar on Management for the 21st Century, undated (Box 36, Video 14)
      - A Conversation with Peter F. Drucker and Peter M. Senge: Leading in a Time of Change, 2001 (Box 36, Video 15)
      - The Peter F. Drucker Foundation - Showcase on Innovation, 1991 (Box 36, Disk 1)
      - Conference video clips, 1991 (Box 36, Disk 2)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Welcome pt. 1 (Box 36, Disk 3)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Jim Collins pt. 2 (Box 36, Disk 4)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Peter Drucker and Jim Collins discussion (Box 36, Disk 5)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Warren Bennis (Box 36, Disk 6)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference - Warren Bennis pt. 2 (Box 36, Disk 7)
      - Self-Assessment Tools Presentation, 1998 (Box 36, Disk 8)
      - SAT Work Session/Michele Hunt, 1998 (Box 36, Disk 9)
      - Michele Hunt presentation, 1998 (Box 36, Disk 10)
      - Self-Assessment Tool Work presentation - Frances Hesselbein closing, 1998 (Box 36, Disk 11)
      - Esther Dyson, Jim Collins, etc. Roundtable cont'd, 1998 (Box 36, Disk 12)
      - Roundtable with Esther Dyson, Jim Collins, etc. pt. 3, 1998 (Box 36, Disk 13)
      - Final Roundtable cont'd, 1998 (Box 36, Disk 14)
      - Leonard Schlesinger presentation pt. 1, 1998 (Box 36, Disk 15)
      - Awards ceremony, 1998 (Box 36, Disk 16)
      - Parish Partnership Transitional Housing Program - Lutheran Family and Children's Services of Missouri: Innovation Award winner, 1992 (Box 36, Disk 17)
      - Project Teamwork - Center for Study of Sport in Society: Innovation Award winner, 1993 (Box 36, Disk 18)
      - Community Schools - Children's Aid Society: Innovation Award winner, 1994 (Box 36, Disk 19)
      - ECO-O.K. Banana Project - Rainforest Alliance: Innovation Award winner, 1995 (Box 36, Disk 20)
      - Second Family Program - Lutheran Social Services of Illinois: Innovation Award winner, 1996 (Box 36, Disk 21)
      - Computer Clubhouse - The Computer Museum: Innovation Award winner, 1997 (Box 36, Disk 22)
      - Times Square Jobs Training Program - Common Ground Community: Innovation Award winner, 1998 (Box 36, Disk 23)
      - California Transportation Training Institute - California Emergency Foodlink: Innovation Award winner, 1999 (Box 36, Disk 24)
      - Peer Educator Training Program - SAGE Project, Inc.: Innovation Award winner, 2000 (Box 36, Disk 25)
      - The Eloy Model/Florence Immigrant and Refugee Rights Project - Innovation Award winner, 2001 (Box 36, Disk 26)
      - Crafts with Conviction - Crayons to Computers: Innovation Award winner, 2002 (Box 36, Disk 27)
      - The Drucker Foundation Self-Assessment Tool for Nonprofit Organizations presentation, 1990s (Box 36, Disk 28)
      - Nonprofit Leader of the Future parts 1 and 2, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Disk 29)
      - Nonprofit Leader of the Future parts 3 and 4, 1997-1998 (Box 36, Disk 30)
      - Chrysalis, 1997 (Box 36, Disk 31)
      - The Drucker Foundation Nonprofit Management Seminars: The Donor Constituency, 1990s (Box 36, Disk 32)
      - The Drucker Foundation Nonprofit Management Seminars: Mission and Strategy, 1992 (Box 36, Disk 33)
      - Peter Drucker Foundation - Meeting the Collaboration Challenge, 2001 (Box 36, Disk 34)
      - Peter Drucker on Redefining Leadership - Organization of the Future conference, 1999 (Box 36, Disk 35)
      - Peter Drucker on Innovation, 1990s-2000s (Box 36, Disk 36)
      - Peter Drucker on Accountability and Self-Assessment, 1990s-2000s (Box 36, Disk 37)
      - Conference - Philadelphia, November 18, 2002 (Box 36, Disk 38)
      - Conference - Philadelphia, November 19, 2002 (Box 36, Disk 39)
      - Conference - Philadelphia: Afternoon sessions, November 19, 2002 (Box 36, Disk 40)
      - Drucker Photos - Philly conference, November 17, 2002 (Box 36, Disk 41)
      - Unlabeled Drucker Foundation conference photos, 1990s-2000s (Box 36, Disk 42-48)
      - Drucker Foundation presentation slides, 1990s-2000s (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Seminar by Satellite photo slides, September 1997 (Box 36, Folder 2-3)
      - 1992 Annual Drucker Conference recordings, November 1992 (Box 37, Cassette 1-8)
      - 1994 Annual Drucker Conference recordings, November 1994 (Box 37, Cassette 9-15)
      - 1997 Annual Drucker Conference recordings, October 1997 (Box 37, Cassette 16-29)
      - 1998 Annual Drucker Conference recordings, November 1998 (Box 37, Cassette 30-41)
      - 1999 Annual Drucker Conference recordings, November 1999 (Box 37, Cassette 42-52)
      - 2000 Annual Drucker Conference recordings, November 2000 (Box 37, Cassette 53-67)
      - PFDF Day - Tape 1, 1980s-1990s (Box 37, Cassette 68)
      - PFDF Day - Tape 2, 1980s-1990s (Box 37, Cassette 69)
      - PFDF Day - Tape 3, 1980s-1990s (Box 37, Cassette 70)
      - "#2 spill; 10 mins", undated (Box 37, Cassette 71)
      - Drucker Foundation Fall conference photo negatives and contact sheets, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Drucker Foundation conference photo negatives and contact sheets, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Drucker Foundation Teleconference photo negatives and contact sheets, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Drucker Foundation conference photo negatives and contact sheets, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Drucker Foundation conference photo negatives and contact sheets, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - "The Computer Clubhouse" photo negatives, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Drucker event photo negatives, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Drucker Foundation conference photo negatives and contact sheets, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Drucker Foundation Fall conference photo negatives and contact sheets, 1999 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Unmarked open reel audio tape, 1988, undated (Box 48)
      - Unmarked open reel audio tape (Box 50)
      - Unmarked open reel audio tape (Box 51)
    - The Leader to Leader Institute, 2003-2011; 2.
      - Innovators: Lessons from the Social Sector - Nan Stone interview part 1, December 7, 2005 (Box 40, Video 1)
      - Innovators: Lessons from the Social Sector - Nan Stone interview pt. 2, December 7, 2005 (Box 40, Video 2)